(Leonard:)Okay, never mind.
(Dave:)Amy, I'm never washing
this hand again.
(Leonard:)You really should.
60 seconds.
(Raj:)This is not looking good.
(Sheldon:)One minute is
a long time.
(Howard:)I've been telling women that
for 20 years.
(Sheldon:)45.
45 seconds is
(Sheldon:)plenty of time for a woman
to walk through that door
(Sheldon:)and fall in love with me.
(Sheldon:)You know, probably half that
if I break out the old cow eyes.
30 seconds.
(Sheldon:)Uh-oh.
(Sheldon:)What if it's Jennifer Lawrence?
(Sheldon:)What?
Oh, that last Hunger Games
was not my cup of tea.
(Howard:)You thought she was great
in X-Men.
(Sheldon:)Oh, fine... I won't shut my heart
(Sheldon:)to the love
of Jennifer Lawrence.
Guys, 15 seconds.
Maybe she's waiting to show up
(Howard:)at the last possible moment.
(groans)
(Sheldon:)Sounds like a drama queen.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no.
It is Jennifer Lawrence.
(Amy:)Five...
(Dave:)four...